eonenergy.com 2019-07-02

# Privacy

#### This statement explains how we collect, use, transfer and store your personal data.  

##  Privacy notice 

Our priority at E.ON is keeping your data secure and treating it with respect. We aim to handle your data fairly and lawfully at all times. We're also committed to being transparent about what we do. This statement explains how we collect, use, transfer and store your personal data. We know that there is a lot of information here, but it's important that you understand your rights as a customer.      

It’s likely that we will update this notice from time to time in order to reflect changes in the law and/or to our privacy practices, but we will notify you of any significant changes. Our website will always show the most up to date version. You can request a paper copy, including large print or braille, by calling us.

##  Who's responsible for your data? 

We refer to 'E.ON' in this statement. This means E.ON UK plc, and the companies owned by E.ON UK plc who provide energy and related products and services. E.ON UK plc is part of the E.ON group, one of the world's largest power and gas companies.

E.ON is the 'Data Controller' for your personal data. This means we have legal responsibility for how we collect and handle your data.

##  How can you contact us? 

We can be contacted at:

**Newstead Court, Little Oak Drive, Annesley, Nottinghamshire, NG15 0DR**

E.ON’s Data Protection Officer has overall responsibility for the way that E.ON collects and handles personal data. The Data Protection Officer can be contacted at the address above.

Other ways to contact us are on our contact us page.

##  Who does this statement apply to? 

Customers and prospective customers 

Individuals, sole traders, partnerships and companies (to the extent that the relevant company provides us with any personal data - for example employee names and e mail addresses)

People we wish to promote products and services to

People who contact us on social media

People who visit our website

##  Other information in this statement 

Your rights

How long we keep your information for

How we keep your information safe

What happens if we send your data out of the EU
